Seino, hi! I'm Chacivre! Yay!
So, today is the day!
Pang!
Pow!
Pan! Pan!
Pan!
Strong! So strong!
It felt so strong!
Pang!
I'd like to introduce you to our newest Ice Pride
I'd like to introduce you to our newest Ice Pride, Elhuikh!
I saw it for the first time!
Oh no!!! I'm so excited!
You've never seen anything like this before!
Oh, really?
No, no, no, no, no!
It was a month ago.
Are you watching this? Gentlemen!
Yes, I'm watching it!
It's getting pretty awesome!
It's so great!
But the scene when he ripped it off was pretty...
But he was my type!
Yes, yes, yes!
So much, so much, so much!
So much!
I have these thoughts, but...
I'm going to see it right away!
Wow!
I'm feeling a little lucky!
First things first.
I'm here! Like that!
This is where it all starts?
Planet...
Shall we go?
I'm going!
Let's see where we go from here.
Let's go!
The big... battle!
Whoa! Wait!
Everyone take a picture!
Good morning.
He's so cute.
Oh, man.
That's how it starts.
It does?
It's a drama scene, right?
Oh, wow.
My parents.
That's the day we met.
Oh!
Here.
I found it.
It's here.
Yes, it's there.
Volentary Aman.
Great, guys.
There it is.
He's talking bare-knuckled.
I'm curious.
It's beautiful.
I didn't know it looked like this.
Beautiful.
Long eyelashes.
I have big hands.
Too big.
I'm so tight!
I like Yuuka
It's too big!
Oh, it's cut!
Yeah, it's amazing!
It's like a rat!
Hey, it's got reflections.
I love it.
I'm really tired.
Hey, dekucho, dekucho, are you okay?
Hey, Yusaki...
Yusaki, Yusaki...
He's crying.
This is TVB
Singing a song
Everyone like this
can make such a sad expression
It's true.
It's nice.
You know, I was playing with this camera thing.
I was playing with it.
Buy her some flowers.
Oh, my God.
They're ours.
Where are you going?
Turn it off and don't turn it on.
It's inside me.In my
I see a dream
The moon is beautiful when I look up
Oh! That's good!
So many songs.
Oh! Nakamura, that's amazing!
This is like a rainbow.
Wow!
Nice!
It's going this way.
It's only a moment It's ours
Dreams are the only things we should never give up
It's gonna be fun.
Smells great.
I'm trying.
At the end of the day.
At the end.
Smile.
I'm gonna get you drunk.
I'm doing it.
Drunk.
And you know what?
When people are still serious.
That's it.
That's so cute.
They filmed us here.
Oh, yeah.
Sleeping... sleeping...
Sleeping, sleeping, sleeping.
He's having so much fun.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
That was nice.
He's so cute.
He was so cute.
She had so much personality.
It's like candy on top of candy.
And you know what?
The one taken at night was used more than the one taken in the morning.
The ones taken at night were used more often than the ones taken in the morning.
Everyone likes it.
We're getting to know each other.
You guys cut a lot of slack in one day.
Really.
Toward the end.
Reach for it.
It hurts.
I don't know how you do it.
That place is amazing.
I feel so pretty.
I can't help it.
You don't do that very often.
I didn't think I'd ever done it before.
I'm serious.
There's a lot of people here. I have to do my best.
You're right.
He's cute.
They're coming.
Hey, listen, later.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Wow, he's stretching.
Wow, he's stretching it.
He's stretching it. He's stretching it.
It would be nice if it became something thrilling.
Laughs.
That's the kind of score.
Let's do it.
If you could all take a look at this.
Reach for my hand.
It's so good!
It's so cute!
May I have a word?
It's Mr. Seizo.
May I?
I know.
There was a scene where they looked alike.
A cute scene.
Wasn't it?
This one...
I know it when I see it.
Where is it?
Next?
This one.
Here!
She really said "goo".
She was asleep.
She was snoring.
With that real sleep look on her face.
It's just one person, so it's real.
It was so real.
Like, which one?
He's snoring.
And my husband...
And his stomach was growling.My stomach was growling, too.
It was quite a rumbling.
She said she was hungry.
Really?
It's so real.
It was morning.
That's sweet.
That's the best level of filming I've ever seen.
Yes, it is.
White looks good on you.
Wow!
So cute.
Yes, sir.
Let me introduce you.
Various
Points
We have a lot of great points.
I hope you will find your own point of interest.
and find your own point of reference.
I would be happy if you could spread the word
I would be very happy if you could write about it.
Thank you very much.
See you soon!
If you like it, please click the Good button and subscribe to our channel!
That's all for now, this is Sentimental!
True love is a noble thing